{
    "id": "1c50d51796d24fe892cf068b98000dce",
    "title": "Adjective Clauses",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The girl ........................................ won the first prize is my niece.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "18750f0957cf47c7b57e425f46e384e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The forest through ........................................... we travelled was dark and gloomy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3229fe9ac76e424dbeb8bb3275fc7222"
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister ............................................. lives in Mexico is a nurse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b168fe67ea74e80851e5d595aa11707"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the same house ......................................... Tennyson occupied.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "who",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4eadc56c631749629f1acfcc6e27eee2"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the same old story .................................................. we have been hearing since our childhood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8aefe6750ad7484092db0e036557ff9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a brilliant son .................................................... is certain to bring credit to his family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7b1292255cc14ff29f28d853888a0cda"
        },
        {
            "question": "All ................................................. glitters is not gold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0a91337f58d644a5bdc9dbed6de2d38d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................................................ is down fears no fall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b55548961db94c0a84dfa7113228a883"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plan .................................................... I proposed was rejected.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "065de8994a8047628d78982aeee838b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the reason ................................................. he does not want to come here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "why",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dec39e8629a24b008718582a2b6f2069"
        }
    ]
}